A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.9-SG 1.13 (A83-A87) FA479
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 86), 1965-1991; 1979-1985; 1.12; 67.2 Cubic Feet; 56 standard record storage boxes - Box R2305-R2360.
  - Brazil, 305
    - Brazil - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Carmo Neto, Dionisio Gomes do, 1980-1984 (Box R2347)
      - Coelho, Isais, 1979-1983 1985 (Box R2347)
      - Franco Filho, Emmanuel, 1981-1984 (Box R2347)
      - Laudari, Carlos A., 1981-1983 1985 (Box R2347)
      - Lenzi, Henrique L., 1979-1983 (Box R2347)
      - Reesink, Marcelle, 1980-1983 (Box R2347)
    - Brazil - Population Sciences, P
      - CEMICAMP - Conference, 1984-1985 (Box R2347)
      - University of Bahia - Health effects of NORPLANT, 1981 1983-1985 (Box R2347)
  - Colombia, 311
    - Fundación para la Aplicación y Enseñanza de las Ciencias - Donation of equipment, 1983 (Box R2347)
    - Colombia - Humanities and Arts, R
      - Universidad del Valle - Humanities equipment, 1970-1977 1979-1982 1984 (Box R2347)
    - Colombia - Social Sciences, S
      - University of the Andes - Population studies, 1976-1986 S (Box R2348)
  - Costa Rica, 313
    - Costa Rica - Medical Sciences, A
      - University of Costa Rica - Field studies, 1981-1984 (Box R2349)
  - Ecuador, 317
    - Ecuador - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Tola, Jaime E., 1979-1983 (Box R2349)
  - Guatemala, 319
    - Guatemala - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Ruano Andrade, Sergio R., 1977-1984 (Box R2349)
  - Mexico, 323
    - Mexico - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Esquivel Alvarez, Claudio, 1981-1985 (Box R2349)
      - Estrella-Chulin, Nestor, 1980-1984 (Box R2349)
      - Macias-Laylle, Joaquin A., 1980-1984 (Box R2349)
      - Villaipando I., Jose F., 1978-1984 (Box R2349)
    - Mexico - Population Sciences, P
      - Colegio de México - Demography fellowships, 1981-1985 (Box R2349)
      - Colegio de México - Population and development conf., 1983-1984 [?] (Box R2349)
  - Peru, 331
    - Peru - Medical Sciences, A
      - Bustamante, Ernesto, 1981-1985 (Box R2349)
    - Peru - Population Sciences, P
      - AMIDEP - Women and development workshop, 1981-1985 (Box R2350)
    - Peru - Social Sciences, S
      - Catholic University - Population fellowships, 1978-1981 (Box R2350)
  - Dominican Republic, 335
    - Dominican Republic - Social Sciences, S
      - Technological Institute of Santo Domingo - Population, 1977-1983 [?] (Box R2350)
  - England, 401
    - Science Policy Foundation - Change, 1982-1984 [?] (Box R2350)
    - England - Medical Sciences, A
      - Imperial College of Science and Technology - Helminths, 1982-1985 (Box R2351)
  - Australia, 410
    - Australia - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Byers, Stephen W., 1980-1984 (Box R2351)
  - Canada, 427
    - Canada - Medical Sciences, A
      - Canadian Institute for Advanced Research - Population health, 1982-1984 (Box R2351)
      - University of Toronto - Filariasis, 1982-1985 (Box R2351)
      - University of Western Ontario - Family medicine, 1981-1983 (Box R2351)
      - University of Western Ontario - Medical care, 1980-1983 (Box R2351)
  - Ceylon, 462
    - Ceylon - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Sarvodaya Shramadana Movement, 1980-1984 (Box R2351)
  - India, 464
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Fernandez, Marilyn, 1981-1984 (Box R2351)
      - Gonsalves, Julian F., 1978-1984 (Box R2351)
      - Pakrasi, Pranab L., 1980-1984 (Box R2352)
      - Rao, M.R., 1982-1985 (Box R2352)
  - Bengal, 466
    - Bengal - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Saha, Arun K., 1979-1984 (Box R2352)
  - China, 601
    - China - Medical Sciences, A
      - Information System for Medical Libraries - Conference, 1982 (Box R2353)
      - Sichuan Medical School - Health Services, 1981-1983 (Box R2353)
    - China - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Chen Da-Yuan, 1980-1984 (Box R2353)
      - Guo Jian Zhong, 1981-1985 (Box R2353)
      - Lu, Gui-Shen, 1979-1983 (Box R2353)
      - Shen Xiao-Zhan, 1980-1983 1985 (Box R2353)
      - Shi Qi-Xian, 1981-1984 (Box R2353)
      - Tsong Shu-Dong, 1979-1981 (Box R2353)
      - Wang Linfang, 1979-1983 (Box R2353)
      - Zhang Chong-Li, 1980-1984 (Box R2353)
  - Japan, 609
    - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Fukuoka, Hideoki, 1981-1983 (Box R2353)
      - Sato, Eimei, 1981-1984 (Box R2353)
      - Tanabe, Kiyoo, 1979-1982 1984 (Box R2353)
      - Tanaka, Toshinobu, 1980-1983 (Box R2354)
  - Korea, 613
    - Korea - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Min, Kyonghee, 1981-1984 (Box R2354)
  - Thailand, 617
    - Thailand - Medical Sciences, A
      - Khon Kaen University - Chronic diseases, 1981-1984 (Box R2354)
    - Thailand - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Kasetsart University - Food and agriculture policy, 1980-1986 [?] (Box R2354)
    - Thailand - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Bhanupongse Nidhiprabha, 1979-1985 (Box R2355)
      - Bundit Jarimopas, 1978-1984 (Box R2355)
      - Charas Kitbamroong, 1980-1985 (Box R2355)
      - Chareinshuk Rajanaridpiched, 1979-1983 (Box R2355)
      - Chiradej Chamswarng, 1980-1984 (Box R2355)
      - Chinnaphong Bumrungsup, 1977-1985 (Box R2355)
      - Chucheep Piputisitee, 1978-1984 (Box R2355)
      - Jeerasak Pongissanupichit, 1974-1984 (Box R2355)
      - Sompop Kassuma, 1978-1985 (Box R2355)
      - Vuthiphong Priebjrivat, 1977-1985 (Box R2355)
  - ICLARM - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management, 626
    - Watanabe, Wade O., 1982-1985 (Box R2355)
  - Netherlands, 650
    - Netherlands - Medical Sciences, A
      - State University of Limburg - Conference, 1981-1984 (Box R2355)
  - Indonesia, 652
    - Indonesia - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Azwar, Saifuddin, 1980-1983 (Box R2355)
      - Budiono, Santoso, 1979-1983 (Box R2355)
      - Mohtar, Mas'oed, 1978-1981 (Box R2356)
      - Nasrullah, Mr., 1978-1981 (Box R2356)
      - Setyawan Budiharta, 1978-1983 (Box R2356)
      - Soesanto Tjokrosonto (1st fellowship), 1976-1978 (Box R2356)
      - Woerjono Mangoendidjojo (1st & 2nd fellowships), 1973-1983 (Box R2356)
    - Indonesia - Humanities and Arts, R
      - Gadjah Mada University - Institute of Indonesian Cultural Studies, 1976-1984 (Box R2356)
    - Indonesia - University Development, UD
      - Gadjah Mada University - Agricultural station, 1975-1984 (Box R2356)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Community health programs, 1974-198[?] (Box R2356)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Donation of equipment, 1983 (Box R2357)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Filariasis, 1982-1983 (Box R2357)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Food production, 1981-1984 (Box R2357)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Goat production, 1977-1980 1982-1984 (Box R2357)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Medical staff development, 1975-198[?] (Box R2357)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Population Studies Institute, 1972-198[?] (Box R2357)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Poultry, 1977-1984 S (Box R2358)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Ruminant production, 1979-1985 S (Box R2358)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Student training, 1982-1984 (Box R2358)
  - Italy, 751
    - Italy - Population Sciences, P
      - University of Rome - Gonadatropin inhibitors, 1980-1984 (Box R2359)
  - Sweden, 800
    - Sweden - Population Sciences, P
      - University of Uppsala - Inhibition of progesterone, 1982-1984 (Box R2359)
  - Turkey, 805
    - Turkey - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Foundation for Development Studies, 1979-1985 S (Box R2359)
    - Turkey - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Aruoba, Celik, 1982-1984 (Box R2359)
      - Bulbul, Mehmet, 1981-1983 (Box R2360)
      - Sakar, Dogan, 1977-1983 (Box R2360)
    - Turkey - Social Sciences, S
      - Middle East Technological University - Agricultural price supports, 1979-1984 (Box R2360)
  - Egypt, 812
    - Egypt - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - El-Menabawey, Mohamed, 1979-1982 (Box R2360)
    - Egypt - Population Sciences, P
      - Al-Azhar University - Contraceptive implants, 1979-1985 (Box R2360)
      - Assiut University - Contraceptive implants, 1980-1985 (Box R2360)
      - Assiut University - Health effects of Norplant, 1981-1984 (Box R2360)
      - University of Alexandria - Contraceptive implants, 1980-1986 (Box R2360)
      - Zagazig University - Contraceptive implants, 1981-1985 (Box R2360)
  - Israel, 825
    - Israel - Medical Sciences, A
      - Mirelman, David, 1983-1985 (Box R2360)
  - Management Training Programs in Developing Countries, 850
    - Management Training Programs in Developing Countries - Venezuela, 339
      - Instituto de Estudios Superiores de Administración - Social development management, 1981-1984 (Box R2360)
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 87), 1978-1987; 1980-1986; 1.13; 42.05 Cubic Feet 32 record storage boxes; 32 standard record storage boxes - Box R2364-R2395.
  Files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 1987.
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120
    - African Development Strategies - Conference, 1983-1985 (Box R2364)
    - Anhyrous Biology - Conference, 1984-1985 (Box R2364)
    - Art and History - Conference, 1983-1986 (Box R2364)
    - Calculus of Terror: Nuclear Strategy - Conference, 1984-1986 (Box R2364)
    - Causes of Backwardness in Eastern Europe - Conference, 1984-1985 (Box R2364)
    - Child Survival - Conference, 1981-1986 (Box R2364)
    - Conflicts & Non-violent Solutions - Conference, 1984-1985 (Box R2364)
    - Decentralized Educational Reform in Five Countries - Conference, 1984-1985 (Box R2364)
    - Detrital Systems for Aquaculture - Conference, 1981 1983-1985 (Box R2364)
    - Evolution of Law within Specific Societies - Conference, 1984-1985 (Box R2364)
    - Food Policy Impact - Conference, 1983-1985 (Box R2364)
    - Foreign Language and International Studies - Conference, 1983-1986 (Box R2364)
    - Future of Health and Health Systems in the Industrialized Societies - Conference, 1983-1986 (Box R2364)
    - Future of Peacekeeping - Conference (not held), 1983-1984 (Box R2364)
    - Gender & Political Culture in the Age of Democratic Revolution - Conference, 1984-1986 (Box R2365)
    - Good Health at Low Cost - Conference, 1984-1986 (Box R2365)
    - Health Statistics in the Year 2000 - Conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2365)
    - Immunomodulation - Conference, 1983-1985 (Box R2365)
    - Infectious Plant Disease - Conference, 1984-1986 (Box R2365)
    - International Banking & Industrial Finance - Conference, 1982-1985 (Box R2365)
    - International Education - Conference, 1984-1986 (Box R2365)
    - International Migration - Conference, 1984-1985 (Box R2365)
    - Intra-ovarian Control Mechanisms - Conference, 1979-1983 1986 (Box R2365)
    - Jewish Literature - Conference, 1981-1984 (Box R2365)
    - Judicial and Legal Elites - Conference, 1984-1985 (Box R2366)
    - National Food Policy - Conference, 1981-1983 [?] (Box R2366)
    - Nuclear Arms Control - Conference, 1984-1985 (Box R2366)
    - Nutrition and Families - Conference, 1984-1986 (Box R2366)
    - Parliamentary Government in Contemporary Western Europe - Conference (not held), 1984-1985 (Box R2366)
    - Post-Nairobi Women & Development - Conference, 1985-1986 (Box R2366)
    - Psychology of Soviet-American Relations - Conference, 1984-1986 (Box R2366)
    - Reflections on Development - Conference, 1983-1986 (Box R2366)
    - Research Priorities in Sub-Saharan Africa - Conference, 1984-1985 (Box R2366)
    - Scholars - Allen, 1983-1986 (Box R2366)
    - Scholars - Barnes, M.J., 1982-1985 (Box R2366)
    - Scholars - Beall, 1984-1986 (Box R2366)
    - Scholars - Bell, L.T., 1984-1986 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Bettelheim, B., 1983-1985 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Birch, A.H., 1983-1987 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Bleikasten, A., 1984-1986 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Botkin, D., 1985-1986 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Burns, J.M., 1984-1985 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Burton, S., 1984-1986 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Busby, G., 1984-1985 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Buvinic, M., 1984-1986 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Checkland, O., 1984-1985 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Checkland, S.G., 1982 1984-1985 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Clark, D., 1984-1985 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Claude, 1984-1986 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Clausen, 1984-1985 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Constable, 1984-1985 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Coppola, C., 1983-1985 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Crichton, 1984-1986 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Dolezelova-Velingerova, 1984-1985 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Fagles, 1983-1985 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Fane, 1984-1985 (Box R2367)
      did not go.
    - Scholars - Forer, 1984-1985 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Fox, P., 1984-1985 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Fuchs, L.H., 1984-1985 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Gelb, 1984-1986 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Georghiou, 1984-1985 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Gibian, 1984-1986 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Gottschalk, 1984-1986 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Hamburger, 1984-1986 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Harleman, 1984-1985 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Hoffman, 1984-1985 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Howze, 1984-1986 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Israel, 1984-1986 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Kallman, 1984-1986 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Kaplan, 1984-1985 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Kelman, 1984-1985 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Kodikara, 1984-1985 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Kolenda, P., 1984-1985 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Kovrig, B., 1983-1986 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Kramish, 1983-1984, 1986 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Korbonski, 1987 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Lamberton, 1984-1986 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Lea, 1984-1985 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Lefcourt, 1983-1985 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Lefcowitz, 1984-1986 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Lock, S., 1984-1986 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Loewald, H.W., 1984-1986 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Luke, 1984-1985 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - McDermott, 1980 1984-1986 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Meijer, 1984-1986 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Minear, 1984-1986 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Nafziger, 1983-1985 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Nash, J., 1985-1986 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Ness, G.D., 1984-1986 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Neurath, 1983-1986 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Nye, J.S., 1984-1985 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - O'Brien, E., 1980-1981 1983-1985 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Pangle, 1984-1985 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Pastore, J., 1983-1985 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Perle, 1982-1984 1986 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Pollard, 1984-1985 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Porter, 1984-1986 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Ranieri, 1984-1985 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Razafindralady, 1987 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Robert, 1984-1985 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Robinson, 1983-1985 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Ruiz-Figueroa, 1983-1985 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Rychlak, 1984-1986 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Sanders, 1984-1985 (Box R2370)
    - Scholars - Schoenberger, 1984-1985 (Box R2370)
    - Scholars - Schorr, 1984-1986 (Box R2370)
    - Scholars - Scott, J.R., 1983-1985 (Box R2370)
    - Scholars - Sherman, 1984-1986 (Box R2370)
    - Scholars - Shloss, C.L., 1984-1986 (Box R2370)
    - Scholars - Silverman, 1984-1986 (Box R2370)
    - Scholars - Simon, 1983-1985 (Box R2370)
    - Scholars - Sjoblom, 1985-1986 (Box R2370)
    - Scholars - Soto Llosa, 1983-1986 (Box R2370)
    - Scholars - Starbuck, 1984-1986 (Box R2370)
    - Scholars - Stokes, E., 1982-1983 (Box R2370)
    - Scholars - Tait, 1983-1985 (Box R2370)
    - Scholars - Tsafriri, 1985-1986 (Box R2370)
    - Scholars - Tyack, 1984-1985 1987 (Box R2370)
    - Scholars - Udvarhelyi, 1984-1986 (Box R2370)
    - Scholars - Vazzana, A.E., 1981-1985 (Box R2370)
    - Scholars - Vivante, 1983-1985 (Box R2370)
    - Scholars - Warren, 1984-1985 (Box R2370)
    - Scholars - Wedgewood, 1985-1986 (Box R2371)
    - Scholars - Westfall, 1984-1985 (Box R2371)
    - Scholars - Zentmyer, 1983-1985 (Box R2371)
    - South Africa: State and Society - Conference, 1985 (Box R2371)
    - Southeast Asia: Moving into the 1990's - Conference, 1983-1986 1990 (Box R2371)
    - Soviet Union and the 3rd World - Conference, 1984-1985 (Box R2371)
    - Subviral Pathogens - Conference, 1982-1984 1986 (Box R2371)
    - Trade Relations - Conference, 1983-1985 (Box R2371)
    - Vectors of Human, Animal and Plant Pathogens - Conference, 1982-1985 (Box R2371)
    - West African Agricultural Research - Conference (not held), 1984-1985 (Box R2371)
    - Women and Agricultural Technology - Conference, 1983-1985 (Box R2371)
  - Research Fellowship for Minority-Group Scholars, 175
    - Research Fellowship for Minority-Group Scholars - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Anderson, Norman B., 1984-1986 (Box R2372)
      - Brown, Ronald E., 1983-1986 (Box R2372)
      - Darling, Marsha J., 1984 1986 (Box R2372)
      - Franklin, Anderson J., 1983-1986 (Box R2372)
      - Jacobs, Wesley C., 1984-1986 (Box R2372)
      - Montejano, David, 1984-1986 (Box R2372)
      - Mukenge, Ida R., 1984-1986 (Box R2372)
      - Oliver[?] Melvin L., 1984-1986 (Box R2372)
      - Randolph, Suzanne M., 1984-1986 (Box R2372)
      - Scott-Jones, Diane, 1983-1985 (Box R2372)
      - Smith, Christopher B., 1984-1986 (Box R2372)
      - Smith, James C., 1984-1986 (Box R2372)
      - Steen, Wayne, 1983 1986 (Box R2372)
      - Valdes, Dennis N., 1984-1986 (Box R2372)
      - Zentella, A.C., 1984-1986 (Box R2372)
  - 188
    - United Nations Association (of the USA) - Family policy, 1983-1986 (Box R2373)
    - Wellesley College - Women and stress, 1984-1986 (Box R2373)
  - 197
    - Abhui Medical College - Clinical epidemiology research, 1984-1985 (Box R2373)
    - Asian regional Network Clinical Epidemiology - Second Annual Meeting, 1975 (Box R2373)
    - First annual meeting, 1983 (Box R2373)
    - Gadjah Mada University - Clinical epidemiology research, 1984 (Box R2373)
    - Khon Kaen University - Clinical epidemiology research, 1984-1986 (Box R2373)
    - Latin American Commission, 1983-1986 (Box R2373)
    - Mahidol University - Clinical epidemiology research, 1984-1986 (Box R2374)
    - McMaster University - International resource center, 1982-1986 (Box R2374)
    - National Institute of Nutrition (Mexico City) - Clinical epidemiology research, 1984-1985 (Box R2374)
    - Paulista Medical School - Clinical epidemiology research, 1984-1986 (Box R2374)
    - Second annual meeting, 1983-1984 (Box R2374)
    - Shanghai First Medical College - Lin, 1983-1984 (Box R2374)
    - Sichuan Medical College - Clinical epidemiology research - Zongnan Ni, 1984-1986 (Box R2374)
    - Sichuan Medical School - Clinical epidemiology, 1980 1982-1986 (Box R2374)
    - Universidad de la Frontera - Clinical epidemiology, 1984-1986 (Box R2374)
  - United States, 200
    - America, Richard F., 1982-1985 (Box R2374)
    - American Citizenship Education Project - Media campaign, 1984 (Box R2374)
    - Center for Employment Training - Computerized System, 1983-1986 (Box R2374)
    - Citizens' Commission on Civil Rights - Voter registration study, 1984-1985 (Box R2374)
    - Columbia University - Employment for minorities in a changing economy, 1981-1986 (Box R2374)
    - Congressional Black Caucus Foundation - Black family conference, 1984-1985 (Box R2375)
    - Educational Fund for Individual Rights - Employment discrimination disputes, 1982-1986 (Box R2375)
    - Employment Program for Minority-Group - Female Single Parents - Community based organizations workshop, 1984 (Box R2375)
    - Institute for Journalism Education - Minorities in the newspaper industry, 1983-1986 (Box R2375)
    - Johnson C. Smith University - Marine Sciences for minorities, 1979-1985 (Box R2375)
    - Joint Center for Political Studies - Civil rights act conference, 1984-1986 (Box R2375)
    - MDC, Inc. - Job training partnership act evaluation, 1983-1986 (Box R2376)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Black administrators conference, 1982-1985 S (Box R2376)
    - NAACP - School segregation, 1974-1986 S (Box R2377)
    - NAACP - (Special Contribution Fund) - Black family summit conference, 1984-1986 (Box R2377)
    - National Bar Association - Conference, 1983-1986 (Box R2377)
    - National Congress of Neighborhood Women - Computerized system, 1983-1986 (Box R2377)
    - National Council of Negro Women - Job training, 1982-1986 (Box R2378)
    - Nelson, Barbara H., 1981-1984 (Box R2378)
    - New York University - "Brown Plus Thirty" conference, 1983-1984 1986 (Box R2378)
    - Opportunities Industrialization Center of Rhode Island - Computerized system, 1983-1986 (Box R2378)
    - Puerto Rican Legal Defense and Education Fund - Employment discrimination, 1982-1986 (Box R2378)
    - Robinson Foundation - Development office, 1981-1986 (Box R2379)
    - Rutgers University - Civil rights conference, 1983-1986 (Box R2379)
    - Stanford University - Hispanic survey, 1983-1986 (Box R2379)
    - University of Chicago - Allison Davis Symposium, 1983-1986 (Box R2379)
    - Urban League of Atlanta - Computerized systems, 1983-1985 (Box R2379)
    - Vera Institute of Justice - Job path manual, 1983-1985 (Box R2379)
    - Voter Education Project - Voter registration, 1984-1985 (Box R2379)
    - Wesleyan University - International development career guide, 1983-1984 (Box R2379)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, A
      - Academy of Natural Sciences - Snails, 1982-1985 (Box R2379)
      - Coker-Vann, Millicent R., 1984-1985 (Box R2379)
      - Cornell University - Infantile diarrhea (in Haiti), 1980-1983 (Box R2379)
      - Cuyahoga County Hospital Foundation - Magnetometer, 1983-1984 (Box R2379)
      - Hillyer, George V., 1984-1986 (Box R2379)
      - Lizardi, Paul M., 1983-1986 (Box R2379)
      - Marine Biological Laboratories - Biology of parasitism, 1979-1983 S (Box R2379)
      - Nogueira, Nadia, 1984-1985 (Box R2380)
      - Princeton University - Data, 1982-1986 (Box R2380)
      - Rand Corporation - Medical procedures conference, 1982-1987 (Box R2380)
      - Ravetch, Jeffrey V., 1984-1986 (Box R2380)
      - Scripps Clinic and Research Foundation - CS proteins, 1983-1986 (Box R2380)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Cleveland, Thomas Edward III, 1982-1985 (Box R2380)
      - Samuels, Fred Gene, 1982-1986 (Box R2380)
      - Sweezy, Robert Rhys, 1983-1986 (Box R2380)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, R
      - Abraham Lincoln Brigade - Archives, 1980-1983 (Box R2380)
      - American Center for Students & Artists (Paris) - Artists-in-residence, 1979-1986 (Box R2380)
      - American Center for Students & Artists (Paris) - Artists-in-residence (SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL) (Box R2381)
      - American Council of Learned Societies - Travel grant program, 1982-1986 S (Box R2381)
      - American Historical Association - Project 87, 1978-1979 1981-1983 1985 (Box R2381)
      - American Historical Association - Project 87 (SUPPL. MATERIAL) (Box R2382)
      - Ashley, Robert R., 1984-1986 (Box R2382)
      - Aspen Institute - Fellowships and seminars, 1982-1985 S (Box R2382)
      - Bowdoin College - Music festival, 1982-1985 (Box R2382)
      - Brookings Institution - U.S. Constitution, 1983-1987 1993 [S] (Box R2383)
      - Byrd Hoffman Foundation - Wilson, 1977-1984 1986 [S] (Box R2383)
      - Carnegie-Mellon University - History and social science program, 1980-1985 (Box R2383)